<!-- WIP
	Orchid water delivery, orchid sector requirement. Unique sector?
-->
<event name="GB_DISPATCH_ORCHID_WATER">
	<text>Your terminal lights up with an urgent message with your dispatcher waiting on the other end of the line. "Dispatcher here. Priority delivery this time 'round. We've got word of a floral settlement that needs some heavy lifting. Water tanks, you're interested?"</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Accept the mission.</text>
		<event>
			<quest event="GB_DISPATCH_QUEST_ORCHID_WATER"/>
			<!-- R4: Note, need to find out how to give an internal water augment under the "water_supply_list" list here. Making an aug list to future proof this with anything in the future-->
			<text>Water is vital across the universe to help settlements grow and prosper. This is even more true for the Orchids who depend on it for their health and well being both physically and spiritually. With the ongoing conflicts throughout the galaxy there has never been a higher demand for water than in these parts during these trying times. The Florals depend on the Federations Spacelift Command to aid them whenever their reserves run dry. Unfortunately, our ship doesn't carry nearly enough water for the delivery so we must rendezvous with a contact to make a pick up the shipment before you can deliver it to the settlement. Your dispatcher has already gone ahead and plotted the location of the contact, as well as giving you a warning: "The floral settlement is depending on this delivery but they are not the only ones who are desperate. These are dangerous times so keep your head on a swivel. Dispatcher, out."</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Plot a course to the rendezvous site.</text>
				<event load="GB_CALL_QUESTION"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Decline the mission and do something else.</text>
        <event/>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="GB_ORCHID_DESPERATE_PIRATES_WATER">
	<preventQuest/>
	<beaconType id="map_icon_none" global="false"> <!-- no map beacon-->
		<color r="0" g="0" b="0" a="0"/>
		<unvisitedTooltip>An unvisited location.</unvisitedTooltip>
		<visitedTooltip>Explored location. Nothing left of interest.</visitedTooltip>
		<undiscoveredTooltip>An unvisited location.</undiscoveredTooltip>
	</beaconType>
	<text>The serenity of this beacon has been disrupted violently by an explosion off the port bow! It came from what was an unidentified ship, now made clear to be a pirate which fired a warning shot to catch your attention. The ship hails you and a feed flicks on of a dry and wilted Orchid crew onboard, "These droughts have been relentless and very harsh on our people. I... we are sorry, sir, but we have heard of your shipment and we'll be taking it. Please, we don't want to fight! We want to save our people!" As hard as it may be, you simply do not have enough water tanks to distribute between these desperate pirates and the settlement. Perhaps there could be a compromise but regardless it'll be a difficult choice to make.</text>
	<ship load="SHIP_PIRATE_ALL" hostile="false"/> <!-- R4: We should change to an orchid pirate specifically-->
	
	<choice hidden="true" req="water_supply_list" lvl="0" max_group="0" blue="false">
		<text>Explain that you have already delivered your shipment, you have no shipment for them to take.</text>
		<event load="GB_WATER_PIRATE_SHIPMENT_DELIVERED"/>
	</choice>
	
	<choice hidden="true" req="water_supply_list" lvl="1" max_group="0" blue="false">
		<text>Try and explain to them that the settlement is also in dire need of water, you can't make a detour.</text>
		<event load="GB_WATER_PIRATE_CHOICE_1"/>
	</choice>
	
	<choice hidden="true" req="water_supply_list" lvl="1" max_group="0" blue="false">
		<text>Promise that their people will get a delivery in due time, the federation won't forsaken this system.</text>
		<event load="GB_WATER_PIRATE_CHOICE_2"/>
	</choice>
	
	<choice hidden="true" req="water_supply_list" lvl="1" max_group="0" blue="false">
		<text>The settlement could go for another couple months if they ration their supply, divert course to the 'pirates' home system!</text>
		<event load="GB_WATER_PIRATE_CHOICE_3"/>
	</choice>
	
    <!-- R4: For those who want to play morally gray, will allow them to attack these poor sods regardless -->
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>We do not negogiate with pirates, order a general alert: All crews to battle stations!</text>
		<event>
			<text>"No, please! Our planet is dying! Famines! Droughts! We don't have mu-" "you cut communications. We need to keep our heads focused. We've got a mission to complete and we won't let a few pirates get in our way. Weapons charging!</text>
            <choice>
                <text>Continue...</text>
                <event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
            </choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="GB_WATER_PIRATE_SHIPMENT_DELIVERED">
	<text>You try to explain to them that you have already delivered your shipment and that there is no shipment they can take from you. Though they say nothing to you they begin speaking to each other in their orchid sign language. Moving slowly with their wilted and dry bodies in an almost heart wrenching display before they eventually recompose themselves and begin speaking to you once more. "We... I do not understand... What are we supposed to do now? Our people... our world is dying..."</text>
	<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_FEDERATION_ELITE" lvl="0" max_group="0">
		<text>Promise that the Federation will not forsaken their world. Support will come!</text>
		<event load="GB_WATER_PIRATE_PROMISE_LIST"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_FEDERATION_ELITE" lvl="1" max_group="0">
		<text>(Federation Elite Crew) Promise that the Federation will not forsaken their world. Support will come!</text>
		<event>
			<text>Though they do not seem confident</text>
			<weapon name="GIFTLIST_KERNEL" />
			<autoReward level="MED">missiles</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Promise that you will go out of your way to help their world.</text>
		<event>
			<text>It will most likely come out of our own pockets, but we can not ignore their pleas and abandon their world. The orchids seem tentatively thankful and transmit the coordinates to their system for you to deliver the shipment too once you have acquired the goods.</text>
			<quest event="GB_WATER_PICKUP_PIRATE"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>We can't do anything here. Prepare to leave.</text>
		<event load="GB_WATER_PIRATE_LEAVE_LIST"/>
	</choice>
</event>


<eventList name="GB_WATER_PIRATE_PROMISE_LIST">
	<event load="GB_WATER_PIRATE_FIGHT"/>
	<event>
		<!--<text>You try to assure them that the Federation will not abandon their system but they are uncertain of the legitimacy of your claim or are otherwise unconfident in the Federation itself. Thankfully, however, they do not escalate the situation further and despite the impasse they eventually powered down their weapons and eventually jumped away.</text> -->
		<text>No matter how much you try to convince them that there is hope you can see nothing but despair on their wilted faces. After a long pause during the standoff they eventually cut communications completely. You assumed that a fight was imminent, but they began to charge up their FTL drives shortly before jumping away  without further incident. A sad day to see the once peaceful orchid sectors tainted by the increase of pirate activity, even more so to see such despairing orchids turning to such desperate measures...</text>
		<instantEscape />
	</event>
	
	<event>
		<text>Communications begin to break down as the orchids erupt in fury "The Federation has already abandoned us! While the war rages on the Federation has turned a blind eye to this sector! Millions are dying and the Federation has done nothing to aid us!" Things escalate as another explosion goes off - and this time it was not a warning shot. All hands, battle stations!</text>
		<ship hostile="true"/>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
		</choice>
	</event>
	
	<event>
		<text>In spite of their initial scepticism, you were able to convince them that the Federation will come to their worlds and will do everything that they can to provide aid. Though they do not seem fully confident they are happy enough to let you go, and are even willing to part ways with one of their kernel launchers as a sign of appreciation and a return to their peaceful ways with hopes that some support will come soon.</text>
		<weapon name="GIFTLIST_KERNEL" />
		<autoReward level="LOW">missiles</autoReward>
	</event>
</eventList>

<eventList name="GB_WATER_PIRATE_CHOICE_1_LIST">
	<event>
		<text>You try to explain that you have orders to follow and that attacking this ship will do nothing but reduce the effectiveness and frequency of whatever support the Federation will be able to extend to this sector. Though it doesn't seem to make the orchids any more comfortable with their state they seem to understand and resign, leaving you to continue on your mission without further incident.</text>
	</event>
	<event load="GB_WATER_PIRATE_FIGHT"/>
</eventList>

<eventList name="GB_WATER_PIRATE_LEAVE_LIST">
	<event>
		<text>You attempt to escape further confrontation and begin charging your FTL drive.Though the Orchids seem deeply upset they seem defeated and do not make any attempts to pursue you and allow you to depart without further escalation.</text>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>You attempt to escape further confrontation and begin charging your FTL drive.Though the Orchids seem deeply upset they seem defeated and do not make any attempts to pursue you and allow you to depart without further escalation.</text>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>The Orchids do not seem to wish to allow you to escape. Rather it is to hold your ship hostage or in protest of your departure they have fired another shot and this time it wasn't a warning shot.	All hands, battle stations!</text>
		<ship hostile="true"/>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
		</choice>		
	</event>
</eventList>
<event name="GB_WATER_PIRATE_CHOICE_2">
	<text>You try to assure them that the Federation will not abandon their system and that help will be on their way but they are uncertain of the legitimacy of your claim or are otherwise not confident in the Federation itself. They stare aimlessly at the video display of you before hunching over the terminal and speaking with a soft and pained tone. "Where has the Federation been? It has been many months since a single ship had landed on our worlds... We were told that when we joined the Federation that they were here to offer us help and protection... where are they now?"</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Federation ships has been protecting these worlds!</text>
		<event>
		<text>"They do and that is fair... but we need help here too! We need help!".... they sigh and lay over the furled over the console to test.</text>
	</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" blue="false" req="orchid_chieftain" lvl="0" max_group="0">
		<text>Federation ships will vcome to aid these worlds!</text>
		<event load="GB_WATER_PIRATE_PROMISE_LIST"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="orchid_chieftain" lvl="1" max_group="0">
		<text>(Chieftain Crew) Promise them the Federation will come to these worlds with aid.</text>
		<event>
			<text>With an Orchid Chieftain lecturing them about the importance of order and priorities of our mission, but, in due time the worlds will grow and flourish. The orchids seem to have calmed down and listen to every word the Chieftain has said, taking it to heart. By the end of it they are happy and confident that things will improve soon enough. The Orchids' demeanour seemed to have softened and they ended transmission. Allowing you to pass without further incident, they even passed a scarce amount of resources over before departing.</text>
			<autoReward level="MED">missiles</autoReward>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="GB_WATER_PIRATE_CHOICE_3">
	<text>Without further delay they immediately transmit the coordinates immediately as the captain hunches over the terminal with the crew behind them waving in jubilation. With the coordinates received we now have a new destination to deliver our cargo, along with them following your jump signatures.</text>
	<quest event="GB_DESPERATE_DROUGHT_PLANET_PIRATE"/>
</event>

<event name="GB_WATER_PIRATE_FIGHT">
	<text>The Orchids do not seem to wish to allow you to escape. Rather it is to hold your ship hostage or in protest of your departure they have fired another shot and this time it wasn't a warning shot.	All hands, battle stations!</text>
	<ship hostile="true"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
	</choice>		
</event>

<event name="GB_DISPATCH_QUEST_ORCHID_WATER">
	<img planet="planet_populated_11"/> <!-- R4: Did I set the planet right? -->
	<text>You arrive at a green planet with a floral settlement growing in one of the great plains that stretch across the world, bristled with a few sub-tropical forests and rolling valleys. This node in particular is serene with little space traffic outside of a token patrol of orchid vessels protecting this region of space.</text>
	<choice hidden="true" max_lvl="1" req="water_supply_list" max_group="0">
		<text>Prepare to land at the colony and make your delivery.</text>
		<event> <!-- R4: how do I make it remove the augment? -->
			<text>You make preparations and cross-checks for arrival and delivery. The water tanks are well fastened and secure for descent. The ship creaks and shakes as it descends through the turbulent clouds of the sky before eventually slowing down for a landing at the designated landing pad. The first thing that hits you when bay doors open is the strongly scented air that wafted into the cargo bay. Once the shipment is off loaded with the aid of the dockworkers your payment is transferred along with an on time delivery bonus!</text>
			<autoReward level="HIGH">missiles</autoReward>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="scrap" min="30" max="30"/>			<!-- R4: If I do this does it increase the reward by 30 scrap-->
			</item_modify>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" max_lvl="0" req="water_supply_list" max_group="0">
		<text>We have no cargo, prepare to leave.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You are left admiring the beauty of the system until it is time to spin up the FTL drive and depart.</text>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="orchid_pirate_water_betrayal" max_group="0">
		<text>Prepare to land at the colony and make your delivery.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You plan to break orbit and make landing preparations, however, the orchid pirates have followed your jump signatures straight to the settlement and are incensed at the sight of your betrayal and begin charging their weapons! The orchid settlement below mistaken your intent here as they assume you are collaborating a raid alongside the pirates and to make matters worse they began opening fire on the two of you with anti-ship batteries!</text>
			<ship load="SHIP_NAME" hostile="false"/> <!-- R4: Note, Set to an orchid pirate ship -->
			<environment type="PDS" target="all"/>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>

<event name="GB_WATER_PICKUP_PIRATE">
	<text>A rather boring node compared to the others commonly found within orchid space. An old trade hub set up around one of the moons around a gas giant where ice haulers frequently bring in their latest haul. As good a place as any to find a seller for water, however, it doesn't look like the station is full of the charitable type.</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<event>
			<item_modify>
				<item type="scrap" min="30" max="30"/>
			</item_modify>
			<text>Purchase the water for the full market price. [-30 scrap]</text>
			<augment name="WATER_SUPPLY" />
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Attempt to barter it for a lower price.</text>
		<event load="GB_BARTER_WATER"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="MIND"> <!-- R4: I'll check to see if I did this right when I wake up I think -->
		<text>(Mind Control) Convince them to lower the price.</text>
		<event>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" blue="false" max_group="0">
		<text>Threaten for a lower price.</text>
		<event load="GB_BARTER_WATER_THREAT"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<eventList name="GB_BARTER_WATER">
	<event>
		<text>You go back and forth with the trader trying to barter the prices lower, even bringing up how the Federation rewards those who help it, but it wasn't enough to change the prices any lower than the market value with demand being as high as it is in this sector. They present you their final offer, take it or leave it.</text>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Purchase the water for the full market price. [-30 scrap]</text>
			<event>
				<item_modify steal="true">
					<item type="scrap" min="30" max="30"/>
				</item_modify>
				<augment name="WATER_SUPPLY" />
				<quest event="GB_DROUGHT_DELIVERY"/>
				<text>With the successful trade, you now plot a course for the droughted world given to you by the pirates.</text>
			</event>
		</choice>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Leave.</text>
		</choice>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>Purchase the water at a minor discount. [-25 scrap]</text>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<event>
				<item_modify steal="true">
					<item type="scrap" min="25" max="25"/>
				</item_modify>
				<augment name="WATER_SUPPLY" />
				<quest event="GB_DROUGHT_DELIVERY"/>
				<text>With the successful trade, you now plot a course for the droughted world given to you by the pirates.</text>
			</event>
		</choice>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Leave.</text>
		</choice>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>You barter back and forth with the trader trying to broker a good deal. Be it the kindness of their heart or they pity the orchids during this war. They offer to slash the price half off in exchange for the Federation to remember their charitable acts when this is all over and give in a good word for them.</text>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Purchase the water at a minor discount. [-15 scrap]</text>
			<event>
				<item_modify steal="true">
					<item type="scrap" min="15" max="15"/>
				</item_modify>
				<augment name="WATER_SUPPLY" />
				<quest event="GB_DROUGHT_DELIVERY"/>
				<text>With the very successful trade, you now plot a course for the droughted world given to you by the pirates.</text>
			</event>
		</choice>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Leave.</text>
		</choice>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>You barter back and forth with the trader trying to broker a deal. Rather you pushed too hard or got on their bad side. They noticed they had the price wrong for the water and instead raised it by a few scrap for 'tax'.</text>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Purchase the water for the full market price. [-35 scrap]</text>
			<event>
				<item_modify steal="true">
					<item type="scrap" min="35" max="35"/>
				</item_modify>
				<augment name="WATER_SUPPLY" />
				<quest event="GB_DROUGHT_DELIVERY"/>
				<text>With the 'successful' trade, you now plot a course for the droughted world given to you by the pirates.</text>
			</event>
		</choice>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>This is outrageous! Leave.</text>
		</choice>
	</event>
</eventList>

<!-- <eventList name="GB_BARTER_WATER_THREAT">

<!-- GB_DROUGHT_DELIVERY -->



<!--	◘◘◘◘◘◘◘◘◘◘◘◘◘◘◘◘◘◘◘◘◘
	        MISC EVENTS
		◘◘◘◘◘◘◘◘◘◘◘◘◘◘◘◘◘◘◘◘◘
-->

<!-- R4: Did CG Jr actually start doing the hidden sector for 2.3 back when we were still working on 2.1? Even months later I am discovering things I have never even seen in my own mod -->
<!--<event name="ENTER_BALLISTIC">
	<text load="TEXT_LIGHTSPEED"/>
	<img back="BACKGROUND_LIGHTSPEED" planet="NONE"/>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Continue...</text>
		<event load="LOAD_ATLAS"/>
	</choice>
</event>
<event name="BALLISTIC_WARP">
	<text>Name: Union Controlled Sector
	Type: Uncolonized
	Unique: True
	Dominant Faction: None
	Rebel Threat Level: Medium

	This Sector was the main theatre for the Federation-Mantis war. There is little active conflict here now, and it serves as a melting pot of scavengers from all over the galaxy, rubbing shoulders with Federation Veterans and scores of Mantis scavengers.</text>
	<playSound>lightspeed</playSound>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Exit Hyperspeed.</text>
		<event load="START_BALLISTIC"/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="COORDS" blue="false">
		<text>Reroute.</text>
		<event load="REROUTE_MENU"/>
	</choice>
</event>

<mod:findName type = "event" name = "ATLAS_MENU">
	<mod-append:choice req = "SEC SECTOR_BALLISTIC">
		<text>Proceed to the Abandoned Battlegrounds.</text>
		<event load="BALLISTIC_WARP"/>
	</mod-append:choice>
</mod:findName>-->
