<metadata>
  <title><![CDATA[ GO BALLISTIC 2! ]]></title>
  <threadUrl><![CDATA[ https://www.subsetgames.com/forum/viewtopic.php?f=11&t=38203 ]]></threadUrl>
  <author><![CDATA[ R4V3-0N, porcu93, cgjunior, laszlogasd, Madoktor, RobintheDragon2, Kommandant_Julk, Vertaalfout, Chrono Vortex ]]></author>
  <version><![CDATA[ 2.2.8 ]]></version>
<!--  <description> 1.3 version description 
<![CDATA[ This mod adds several sets of ballistic weapons and drones to the game, including autocannons, gauss, coil guns and railguns, all with unique animations and sounds.

You can also use "ranged weapons" to try to deal a first strike against an enemy, shoot down an incoming threat, and do lots of other things ranged weapons are useful for.

If you want to see if a weapon is ranged, check its tip in the equipment tab.

Making this mod work perfectly with Captain's Edition is a bit of a pain, but it's doable. Despite what the load order in the CE thread says, you'll want to load the mods in this order:
	| GO BALLISTIC! CE Fixes
	| All CE resources, data and patches (in the order specified in the CE thread)
	| GO BALLISTIC! (this mod)
	| GO BALLISTIC! CE Content Patch
	V Any ship mods you are using
]]>
  </description> -->
  
  
  
  <description>
<![CDATA[ This mod adds ballistic weaponry from multiple eras of the Federation, ranging from the Federation-Mantis War's old kinetic weaponry to the Federation Civil War's magnetically driven Gauss Rifles, and even some bleeding edge technologies such as Rail Guns!

This version is built for use with Multiverse 5.3 and introduces mechanics, events, encounters, stores, and features that help immerse and implement it into the overhaul's setting.
LOAD ORDER: Load this after the respective Multiverse files in slipstream mod manager.

Features
    • 18 new ballistic weapons
    • 4 elite weapon versions
    • 3 ballistic weapons with the ability to swap ammo during combat
    • 3 new multiverse renegades including cruiser encounter with its corresponding multiverse renegade loot weapon
    • Various new events, stores, and encounters
    • Early implementation of a few new factions and enemies that will be expanded upon in later updates
    • Compatibility with the Multiverse add-on mod Forgemaster including a cross-over weapon recipe

Based on my previous GO BALLISTIC! 1 developed by Chrono Vortex and myself.
Original autocannon weapon concepts based on the unfinished Foundation of the Federation mod overhaul with permission from WhaleCancer.
Spell checked by BetelgeuseBear, Skye, and JerC.]]>
  </description>
</metadata>
